What's a little romance between exes?
An Unexpected Christmas is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Michael Robinson.
Jamie hasn’t told his family that he and his now ex-girlfriend Emily broke up.
After an inopportune run-in with Emily at the train station in his hometown, Jamie convinces
her to pretend they’re still a couple to avoid ruining Christmas for his family.
Emily, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Jamie, played by Tyler Hynes.
Becca, played by Alison Wandzura.
Diane, played by Lynda Boyd.
Tom, played by Paul McGillion.
Grandma, played by Elan Ross Gibson.
A Castle for Christmas is a 2021 American Christmas romantic comedy film
directed by Mary Lambert, and starring Brooke Shields and Cary Elwes.
Bestselling author Sophie Brown journeys to Scotland, both to avoid outrage towards her latest book and to find inspiration to write her
next one, but she unexpectedly falls in love with a castle – unexpectedly connecting  with its curmudgeonly duke owner.
The film was released on November 26, 2021, by Netflix.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.